lessonplanspage.com 2012-05-10

# LessonPlansPage.com Privacy Policy | HotChalk's Lesson Plans Page

The Lesson Plans Page respects your privacy and will not do anything in violation of your privacy. No personally identifiable information is collected by LessonPlansPage.com. You have the opportunity to subscribe your email address to our newsletter. If you do, your email address will never be given to any third party. You’re welcome to read the details of our privacy policy below:

## **About Us**

> This is a privacy policy for The Lesson Plans Page.
> 
> Our homepage on the Web is located at http://www.LessonPlansPage.com.
> 
> We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy.
> 
> You may contact us by mail at the following address:
>
>> HotChalk, Inc.  
>  1999 S. Bascom Avenue, Suite 1020  
>  Campbell, CA 95008  
>  408-369-9125  
>  (Fax) 408-608-1679
> 
> You may contact us by e-mail at [hceditorial@hotchalk.com](mailto:hceditorial@hotchalk.com).

## **Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals**

> We have the following privacy seals:
> 
>   * **New Dispute** : 
> 
> Contact at: [hceditorial@hotchalk.com](mailto:hceditorial@hotchalk.com)
> 
> 

> 
> **Additional Information  
>  **This policy is valid until 1 Jan, 2038 at 12:00:00 CST.

## **Data Collection**

> P3P policies declare the data they collect in groups (also referred to as “statements”).
> 
> This policy contains 2 data groups.
> 
> The data practices of each group will be explained seperately.
> 
> If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)

### Group “Basic information”

> We collect the following information:
> 
>   * Click-stream data
>   * HTTP protocol elements
>   * Search terms
> 

> 
> This data will be used for the following purposes:
> 
>   * Completion and support of the current activity.
>   * Web site and system administration.
>   * Research and development.
> 

> 
> This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
> 
> The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
>
>> Data collected from all Web users: access logs, and search strings (if entered).

### Group “Cookies”

> At the user’s option, we will collect the following data:
> 
>   * HTTP cookies
> 

> 
> This data will be used for the following purposes:
> 
>   * Research and development.
>   * One-time tailoring.
> 

> 
> This data will be used by ourselves and our agents.
> 
> The following explanation is provided for why this data is collected:
>
>> Cookies are used to track visitors to our site,
>> 
>> so we can better understand what portions of our site best serve you.

## **Cookies**

> Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
> 
> Our site makes use of cookies.
> 
> Cookies are used for the following purposes:
> 
>   * User targeting
>   * Research and development\
> 

## **Policy Evaluation**

> Microsoft Internet Explorer 6 will evaluate this policy’s compact policy whenever it is used with a cookie.
> 
> The actions IE will take depend on what privacy level the user has selected in their browser (Low, Medium, Medium High, or High; the default is Medium.
> 
> In addition, IE will examine whether the cookie’s policy is considered satisfactory or unsatisfactory, whether the cookie is a session cookie or a persistent cookie, and whether the cookie is used in a first-party or third-party context.
> 
> This section will attempt to evaluate this policy’s compact policy against Microsoft’s stated behavior for IE6.
> 
> _Note:_ this evaluation is currently experimental and should not be considered a substitute for testing with a real Web browser.
> 
> _Satisfactory Policy:_ this compact policy is considered _satisfactory_ according to the rules defined by Internet Explorer 6.
> 
> IE6 will accept cookies accompanied by this policy under the High, Medium High, Medium, Low, and Accept All Cookies settings.
> 
> For any questions, please contact [hceditorial@hotchalk.com](mailto:hceditorial@hotchalk.com).

**Third Party Advertising**

> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**Third Party Cookies**

> In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.
> 
> We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
> 
>   * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
>   * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
>   * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
>
